http://www.newzealandwoolsweaters.com/privacy.php?osCsid=c8c00e5d581d69af826af22638df1c32

Checkout
Your cart is empty.
Advanced Search
New Zealand Wool Sweaters offers quality in every garment. Fashionable pashminas, scarves, hats, gloves, vests, socks, vests, sweaters and jackets.
The world's only environmentally friendly fur blend, a soft yet warm blend of Merino Wool, Australian Brushtail Possum Fur and Pure Mulberry Silk.
Naturally pleasing. Naturally New Zealand.
US DollarEuroAustralia DollarNew Zealand DollarPounds
My husband is over the moon with his Forest Fur hat, gloves and scarf, as it is rather cold at the moment. Thank You! ... More Sue, Leicester UK
Home » Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
At Kiwi Enterprises we are determined to protect your privacy.
This document outlines our privacy policy. By shopping at NewZealandWoolSweaters.com, you are accepting the activities described in this Privacy Notice.
What Information Do We Get?
Information given to us by you:
When you use our online shopping facility, you supply us with certain information that is necessary for us to fulfill your order.
Information that is automatically collected:
When you visit any website, you leave a trail of information behind. This may include details about your hardware, which website you came from, how long you stayed, and what pages you looked at. This information is used to improve the website and meet our customer needs better. All information gathered in this way is anonymous. It is not (and can not be) linked, or traced to your account with us in any way.
E-mail address:
We occasionally send out e-mail newsletters.
We may also send e-mails to all customers, with important news or special offers.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this.
We do not release your email address, or any other information about you to any third party. Nor do we use any of your information for any other purpose than to serve your needs with Kiwi Enterprises, LLC.
Cookies:
Our website uses cookies to help us make your visit to our website as enjoyable as possible. A cookie is a small text file that is stored to your computer which contains information that can personalize your visit to a website. It may be used to store regularly used information, such as usernames and passwords or preferences, to save you time, to recognize you when you return to a website, or to provide you with information.
Agents:
We use other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending out orders, processing credit card payments, etc. They have access only to the personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. For example, we have to tell Fedex your name and address!
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Paypal as our sole online payment processor. Your credit card is processed by Paypal, so we NEVER see your credit card number. Paypal protects your privacy and information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input, thereby making your online transactions with us safe and secure.
Company Information
About UsForest FurCustomer FeedbackWool CareFAQSContact UsShopping Information
Wholesale PricingShipping & ReturnsSecurityConditions of UsePrivacy Notice
Copyright © 2020New Zealand Wool Sweaters  Powered by osCommerceSTS PLUS v4.5.8
